# Tom Booth

### Managing Director of LOKE Digital | MD at Aston Club

At LOKE we are digital natives. We transform the way our clients engage with their customers and help them achieve a better return on their marketing investment. With years of experience in digital, our specialised team of marketers, developers, designers and analysts work together to create clear, effective and complete user-driven digital loyalty solutions.

Email: tb@loke.com.au

**EXPERIENCE** 

### **LOKE Digital**

#### **Managing Director**

OCTOBER 2012 - PRESENT (3 YEARS 8 MONTHS)

At LOKE we create branded mobile loyalty applications that combine mobile payments with interactive social content. Our solutions empower our clients to seamlessly reward their customers not only for what they spend but also for promoting their business to their friends. Our team also run Aston Club, Australia's leading mobile payments wallet.

### **Aston Club Pty Ltd**

JUNE 2013 - PRESENT (3 YEARS)

#### **Managing Director**

Aston Club aims to become the industry standard in the mobile payment sector. Through a quick, simple, secure mobile application integrated into the merchant's Point Of Sale, customers of the merchant's can open, manage and settle their accounts via their mobile device. Aston Club is one of the largest providers of mobile payments in the Australian market.

LOKE	Digital
------	---------

MARCH 2012 - OCTOBER 2012 (8 MONTHS)

**Director of Operations** 

Telefirm

FEBRUARY 2009 - FEBRUARY 2012

(3 YEARS 1 MONTH)

**Managing Director** 

Telstra Shop Unley

August 2007 - January 2009 (1 YEAR 6 MONTHS)

Corporate Account Manager

**Telstra Shop Unley** 

APRIL 2006 - APRIL 2007 (1 YEAR 1 MONTH)

**Sales Associate** 

April 2006 - April 2007 (1 year 1 month)

**EDUCATION** 

# **University of Adelaide**

2003 - 2005

# **Prince Alfred College**

1998 - 2002

SACE,

**SKILLS** 

New Business Development, Business Strategy, Strategy Development, Sales Management, Marketing, Business Development, SaaS, Project Management, Operations Management, Management, Strategy, Team Management, Account Management, Social Media, Direct Marketing, Entrepreneurship, Procurement, Customer Service, Social Media Marketing, Small Business, Sales, Mobile Devices, B2B, Business Planning, Digital Marketing, E-commerce, Online Advertising, Marketing Strategy, Telecommunications, Event Management, Marketing Communications, Online Marketing, Start-ups, Integrated Marketing, Strategic Partnerships, Team Leadership, Email Marketing, Mobile Applications, Strategic Planning, Negotiation, Leadership, Advertising

RECOMMENDATIONS

#### Nicholas Birrell

Was Tom's Client

Tom is by far the best, most personable Telstra dealer I have ever come across. As small business telco experts Telefirm handles ALL our telecommunications needs and best of all we have only one Account Manager that understands OUR business, not just theirs. No more spelling my name and giving my date of birth to random customer service reps. If you are with Telstra, go through Telefirm. If you are switching to Telstra, go through Telefirm. Keep up the good work guys!